

Bryan Kenneweg

Global Data Specialist / Junior Developer

About Me

I am a energetic professional with a recent found love for anything web design through UT Austin's Coding Boot Camp.

Anywhere from HTML, CSS (SASS) to Bootstrap and Javascript; if I am able to be create or improve something wonderful, I am at home. In addition to web design, I have a batman utility belt of experience including customer relations, eCommerce, sales and dad jokes.

Experience

GLOBAL DATA SPECIALIST, WHOLE FOODS, AUSTIN, TX - 2016-PRESENT

Support Whole Foods Market suppliers with the maintenance of their data about their products and pricing, as well as forecast trending supplier issues and develop fixes. Additionally, coordinate with regions and other global teams so all have the most accurate supplier data for all business needs.

CUSTOMER RELATIONS, APPLE INC. AUSTIN, TX - 2015-2016

Responsible for COMPLETE ownership of our customers issues while identify creative solutions that not only satisfy, but to delight the customer while balancing company and customer needs. Investigate complex issues using complex tools to resolve the issue in a timely and precise manner. In addition to assisting with on boarding of new hires, mentoring and leading discussion with regarding to new practices, tools or helpful tips.

CUSTOMER SOLUTIONS, EBAY, AUSTIN, TX - 2015-2015

Partner with eBay customers to help them navigate successfully through a challenge or conflict with another eBay customer. Establish trust and relationships between eBay and the community while maintaining a high level of detail and accuracy while focusing on details and creating experiences customers love.

SALES PRODUCER, ALLSTATE, AUSTIN, TX - 2012-2014

Built a personal line of business resulting in 40% increase of sales agency wide. Tapped into different lines of business as well maintained rapport.

Education

University of Texas at Austin – Coding Boot Camp 2017

Austin Community College - Computer Science 2012